Bye, thanks for being my models for a little while.
What do you mean I can't go on this one?
Yuko, calm down.
I want to perform in more guerrilla concerts.
Sorry, but the concert on Akibastar overlaps with it.
Yuko, you'll be taking over Achan's position.
Akibastar's just some boring planet.
But I want to get out of here.
I want to sing on a bigger stage for even more people.
Take that back.
Akibastar is special.
A long time ago, it was ravaged by terrible wars that plunged it into poverty and ruin.
But the people still love their planet dearly.
They spent generations creating the subterranean city.
This place embraces painful situations and sad memories and gives birth to new hope.
That's why people who come to Akibastar love entertainment.
It's not some boring planet.
Akibastar and the 0048 stage, they are our most important and sacred space.
I'm sorry.
Yuko, protect the glow of Akibastar for me.
The glow of Akibastar?
Yes.
In order to do that, you yourself must shine.
If you let it, Akibastar will shine down on you and make you glow even brighter.
I can't wait to see it.
It's not fair, Akibastar.
You told me to protect Akibastar and then ran off somewhere that I couldn't follow.
But there is something I can do now.
It's not fair, Akibastar.
In here, I wonder why she inherited Mariko in the first place.
The other successors seem inspired to dance better.
Especially Chan-Yu.
She's really getting into it.
Yeah, that's my girl.
The trainees seem excited, too.
Lately, Nagichie has been showing progress.
Great progress.
All the other members sparkle when a center nova is about to be born.
That excites you?
Huh?
Don't you remember what you said?
If it's truly your intention to bring back the center nova position, I'll do everything I can to stop you.
Don't tell me you're going back on your work.
Oh, come on, Tsubasa.
Did you forget I used to be a member of Zero Zero?
The members' hearts are always one, remember?
There's no need to be distant.
I still feel the same way as you.
Probably.
Great progress, what a good job!
Come on, we gotta hustle!
Okay.
Don't leave without me!
Wait up!
Mariko, you're a successor now.
Shouldn't you be going home on the bus with the others?
I wanted to take the train home.
Mariko, you shouldn't do something like this.
Successors shouldn't spend so much time with trainees.
Whether someone is a successor or trainee doesn't matter to me.
If I want to ride the train with you guys, I'm going to do it!
Wow!
Mariko-sama, you sounded like a sadist just then!
That gave me chills.
No fair!
Mima, Mari, tease me too!
Tease me, tease me!
Um, that sounds really weird!
This isn't that how you try this train is for us.
Ready up.
Huh?
It's Yuko!
Uh, Yuko-san?
Where?
Over there!
By the turbine!
I-I see someone, but I can't tell if it's Yuko.
Sona does got Hawkeyes on her.
Well, if it is her, what is she doing over there?
Yuko-san.
She really has an amazing voice, doesn't she?
Hold up.
You can hear her?
Mm-hmm.
Now that you mention it, so can I.
Even now I can hear the wind sink, the ground in life's new beginning.
She must really be belting it.
I can't believe we can hear her over the sound of the turbine.
And she's hitting the notes perfectly despite all of the rumbling.
I can feel all of Yuko-san's emotion.
What?
What do you mean?
Even though she took first place at the general elections, she's not satisfied.
It's as though she's shouting that she wants to reach even higher.
But...
What's wrong, Nagisa?
She's too cool.
Huh?
Darn it!
Maybe it was a bad idea to take down the pictures of her I had in my room!
I need to find new ones to hang up in front of!
I have a new holo of Yuko-san if you'd like to have it.
Huh?
As long as you don't mind a holo card with Makoto-san on the back, you're welcome to it.
Oh!
Suzuko!
Even now I can hear the world sing, calling for a new beginning.
And in the sea of despair, we will not drown.
Stop!
Kojuharu, you're behind!
Sorry!
Mariko, look around yourself.
Slide to Tomo-chin's position.
Okay!
Yushiyama-sensei!
What, Yuko?
Would it be alright if I practiced on my own for a little while?
What?
On your own?
Are my lessons too weak for your taste, Ms. Yuko?
That's it.
They're super weak!
Anyway, see you later!
Oh!
The ace suddenly left practice.
You never know when you'll have the opportunity for a good photo.
She's unbelievable.
But she's certainly got the energy.
Guess I'll let it slide.
Yuko-san!
Huh?
Uh-huh!
Uh-huh.
These days she usually acts like her normal self, but sometimes she's difficult to approach.
Just like she was tonight.
It's like she's become a...
She's become a what?
A warrior.
If that makes sense.
I've seen this behavior before.
Huh?
Someone like her.
She laughs with everyone, and is loved by all.
But she… she's not that easy to approach most of the time.
Even when she's with everyone else, somehow she seems alone.
You must be talking about Achan.
Huh? Tsubasa-san?
The 13th generation Achan was like that for a while after she became the Center Nova.
She had an aura that kept people away, and prevented them from speaking to her freely.
Achan, I… I feel like you're becoming increasingly alone.
Alone? Why's that?
I don't know.
I don't even know why I feel that way.
But… everyone here really likes you.
If there's something we can help with, just ask.
I feel like you're fighting on your own. You can rely on us.
Thanks. That means a lot.
I like everyone else as well. I love them.
Thank you for worrying about me, Mariko. I'll work on it.
Achan…
Don't worry. I know that I'm not alone here. So smile for me.
But…
Achan disappeared immediately after that conversation.
Where did the Center Novus disappear to?
That's the question on everyone's mind.
If you could see them again, it would be…
And make this broken world of space before…
You scared me half to death!
And my evil plan to feel your youthful skin is working out nicely!
Holy crap, it's tight!
If you're gonna fondle, at least put on a towel or something first!
Loneliness for us is the price that we all must pay for freedom!
Huh?
Hey, Yuko.
Do you still want to go there, even if the cost is great?
It's closer than you realize.
Huh?
Somewhere no one will bother you.
The sacred position zero.
Position zero?
Buried deep within Archibastar is a massive duolinium deposit.
But greater than that is the Center Nova, the goddess of the sun,
who activates the duolinium and makes the Kuraras shine intensely bright.
I'm so grateful for the miracle that's about to occur.
I may just sing myself.
One, two, three, four!
I want you!
I need you!
I love you!
Atama no nagante lur crafts
Music heavy in off the screen!
Ryuko-san shining out there!
Oh, her stage presence is overwhelming!
She might really be able to become the Center Nova.
But if she becomes the Center Nova...
At the general elections, she said she wouldn't disappear on us.
She'll be fine. I know she will.
The first condition for triggering the Center Nova phenomenon...
A concert on Akibastar.
To be continued...
If you want to become the Center Nova, you have to accept the burden of solitude.
Solitude?
Those who shine bright are always followed by dark shadows.
Fued with jealousy, targeted and constantly used.
Position Zero wholeheartedly takes on all of these headwinds.
But if you're courageous enough to seize that darkness and make it your own,
the position you want to be will also be yours.
I want you, I want you, I need you, I need you.
There's no one there.
Back then, Ah-chan was always right before me.
She may have been protecting me from those strong winds.
I didn't even know they were there to begin with.
But now, she's not there anymore.
And it's my turn to step into the wind.
This is an emergency.
Presidents of Akibastar should evacuate to shelters immediately.
Evaculate?
What's going on up there?
Listen up, everyone.
A massive DES force has crossed our defensive line and is invading.
The trainees have already moved out.
Follow them.
Right.
The second condition for triggering the Sintanova phenomenon.
A concert with some bad weather.
Hey, where is all this lightning coming from?
It's possible that the weather control system was hacked by enemy forces.
For real?
Something's very wrong.
This is definitely not the Akibastar, I know.
Oh!
They're here.
Let's go, everyone!
Protect the planet and the fan!
Oh, no!
No!
This is wrong!
This isn't what they promised!
No!
This is wrong!
This isn't what they promised!
No!
But what?
That's wrong!
This isn't what they promised!
Promised?
What are you talking about!?
Listen to me!
The temple is in great danger!
The D.E.S!
No Zodiac, they're after the Juallium!
And the Cinnor Nova!
Zodiac's behind this?
Koji Estecaru!
Tomachin!
Take the Seventy Sixth Generation
and protect the temple!
What?
The temple!?
If anything happens to Sensei-Sensei,
then all of AKB 0048
and Akiba Star will be finished!
You won't get past that!
Sentry Nova! Sentry Nova!
Sentry Alpha!
Nagisa, behind you!
It hurts. The rain hurts so much.
The train we took to the stage together.
The city we played in together.
The place where we sang together.
Help!
Nagisa!
Stop! The Sentry Nova protects the other members
no matter how strong the headwinds may be!
Nagisa, are you all right?
It's Yuko's head!
Yuko's head!
Can't you pretend to anyone?
Can't you face the wind alone?
Is the flying gat ready to launch?
We need about 15 more minutes.
You've only got five.
Roger.
If this keeps up...
Move, please!
Meechan!
AKB-0048 shines the brightest at concerts.
So we'll give the DES a concert they won't forget.
Oh, the song.
Okay, everyone.
The concert's back on!
What are you talking about, Yuko-san?
We'll do this AKB-0048 style!
We sing, we dance, and fight for love!
In order to protect Akiba star!
TAKE
Phenomenon, a life-threatening battle and concert in one.
Akibastar is the home of our hearts.
We fought to win the freedom of the people who live here, and we will do it again.
Yuko, protect the glow of Akibastar.
You don't have to tell me twice.
There are still so many!
There's no end to these things.
We should go underground!
Oh, shit!
Let's go!
What's that?
Now, let's get inside!
They're burning our stage to the ground!
Stop it now!
The three conditions have been met.
Well done, Michonne.
Well done.
Now all we need is a powerful torrent of emotion.
Hit!
And another one bites the dust.
Tsubasa, we're at our limit here!
Can everyone hear me?
Tsubasa-san?
We're retreating from Akibastar!
You're kidding!
Retreating, why?
They're after Zero-Zero, not the civilians.
Fighting any further would only produce more casualties.
We've got to get away in the flying gett immediately.
But we can't leave Akibastar!
This is an order.
Understood!
I don't get it.
Why is this all happening?
Position Zero.
Where only the True Center is allowed to stand.
Never anyone's understudy.
No one's standing in front of you.
Just you and the wind.
The world I can see from there?
Yuko, what are you doing?
Yuko, come back here!
Please!
Yuko, you have to come back now!
I'm sorry, Tsubasa-san.
I made a promise with Ah-chan that I intend to keep.
I will protect Akibastar.
Count on it!
Yuko!
Wanting to become the Center Nova isn't enough.
I have to become it!
I have to stand in Position Zero.
Even if it means being alone!
No, no!
No, Yuko's eyes!
What?
Where's that glow coming from?
The Kira-ra's glow is protecting Yuko.
The Kira-ras are so excited.
I think she's gonna do it!
She's becoming the Center Nova!
Don't do it!
If Yuko doesn't stop, she's gonna burn up!
What is that?
I don't know.
A gate?
It's the Center Nova, at long last.
Capture the goddess who changes the word!
Now, Tsubasa!
The Center Nova's power is opening the gate!
It's your chance to bring back Ah-chan and the others!
Mi-chan, don't tell me you planned this!
A gate!
Now, let's fight!
Is it mine?
A-blog Camata of Paris?
You can save!
輝くな
ずっと見守ってた
深奥の空から
今僕は雨になろう
Ah 君に捧ぐ
こんな僕に
出来ることは
君の虚しさを
少しでも癒すこと
今僕は雨になろう